import React from "react";

const questions = [
    {question: "Psychology", answer: "The scientific study of behavior and mental processes."},
    {question: "Behavior", answer: "All outward or overt actions and reactions."},
    {question: "structuralism", answer: "Focus of the study is the structure or basic elements of the mind."}, 
    {question: "correlation", answer: "A measure of the relationship between two variables"},
    {question: "single-blind study", answer: "study in which the subjects do not know if they are in the experimental or the control group"}, 
    {question: "double-blind study", answer: "study in which neither the experimenter nor the subjects know if the subjects are in the experimental or control group"}, 
    {question: "dopamine", answer: "attention, learning, movement, cocaine, schizophrenia"}, 
    {question: "serotonin", answer: "mood, sleep, appetite, aggression, depression [too little]"}, 
    {question: "frontal lobe", answer: "emotions; personality, decisions, memory, planning, inhibition"}, 
    {question: "neurons", answer: "soma has the dendrites around it which receives information and send it to the synaptic knobs and turns it into a chemical message"}, 
]

export default questions;